Guide to the Zoe Chandik Birding Field Notes and Slides
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Zoe Chandik Birding Field Notes and Slides
1951-2011
SC1240
Chandik, Zoe
12 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Access Terms
Birds --California.; Slides.
Collection Contents
- Field notes, 1951-2011
  - Bird Lists - 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bird Lists - 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bird Lists - 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bird Lists - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bird Lists - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bird Lists - 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bird Lists - 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bird Lists - 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bird Lists - 1965 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bird Lists - 1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bird Lists - 1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bird Lists - 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bird Lists - 1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bird Lists - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bird Lists - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bird Lists - 1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bird Lists - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bird Lists - 1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bird Lists - 1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bird Lists - 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bird Lists - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Bird Lists - 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bird Lists - 1985 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bird Lists - 1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Bird Lists - 1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Bird Lists - 1988 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Bird Lists - 1989 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Bird Lists - 1990 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bird Lists - 1991 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bird Lists - 1992 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Bird Lists - 1994 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bird Lists - 1995 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Bird Lists - 1996 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Bird Lists - 1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bird Lists - 1998 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Bird Lists - 1999 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Bird Lists - 2000 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bird Lists - 2001 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Bird Lists - 2002 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Bird Lists - 2003 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Bird Lists - 2004 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Bird Lists - 2005 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Bird Lists - 2006 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Bird Lists - 2007 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Bird Lists - 2008 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Bird Lists - 2009 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Bird Lists - 2010 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Bird Lists - 2011 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Hypocolius - UAE etc. 2007 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Plant Lists, 1986-1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Serpentine, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Serpentine Back Organization, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Serpentine Articles, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Serpentine of Bay Area, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - South America - Colombia, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Guatemala, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Australia, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Western Mexico, 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Eastern Mexico, 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Bolivia, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - W. Coast Mexico Habitat India Ators, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - D.S. Jordan Trip Bird Notes, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Hawaii, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Africa, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Baja California, 1973-1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Malaya and Borneo, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - West Indies, 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Costa Rica, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Peru, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - "Sea of Cortez", 1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - New Zealand, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Trinidad and Tobago, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Baja California Natural History, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Trinidad and Tobago, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - National and State Park, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Palo Alto Teaching Aids, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Plant Keys, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Plants of Baja, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Mexican Plant Lists, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Oaxaca/Chiapas, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Zoe's Library, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Bird Lists - 1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - India, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Shells - Gen., undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Montane Ecuador, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Venezuelan Tepuis, 1994 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Philippine Islands, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Oaxaca, Mexico, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Panama, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Atlantic Forest, Brazil, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Argentina, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Suriname, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Accessories, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Papua New Guinea, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Brazil - Rare Bird Reports, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Nepal + England, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Alaska, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Japan, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Cuba, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Chile, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Uganda, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - South + West Africa, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Spain, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - New Caledonia/Australia, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Jamaica, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Birds, Mammals, Fish + Turtle Observations in Eastern Tropical Pacific Ocean by Chandik, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Birds, Mammals, Fish + Turtle Observations in Eastern Tropical Pacific Ocean by Chandik pt. 2, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Ecuador July-August, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Birds of the World: A Check List, 1950-2000 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Ted Chandik's World Bird List, 1950-1991 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Traveler's List and Checklist for Birds of Mexico, 1970-1990 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Kenya + Tanzania, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - David Starr Jordan, Baja California, 1971-1978 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Hawaii, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Mexico (Western), 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Colombia (some Peru + Brazil), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Guatemala + Mexico (Eastern and El Triunfo), 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Australia, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Bolivia, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Mexico (Western, Yucatan/Palengue), 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Jamaica, Dominican Republic + Trinidad & Tobago, 1980, 1983-84 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Argentina, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Mexico (Yucatan + San Cristobol_, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - New Zealand (2 trips), 1984 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Baja California + "Sea of Cortez", 1984, 1985-86 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Costa Rica, 1985-86, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Malaya, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - India, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Papua New Guinea, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Philippines, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Alaska, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Texas, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Japan, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Cuba, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Spain, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Nepal, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Brazil, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Madagascar, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Uganda, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Venezuela + Suriname, 1994, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Chile + Jamaica, 2005, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - South Africa and Sierra Leone, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - UAE + Oman Spain, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - New Caledonia + Australia, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Ecuador (Montane), 2009 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Brazil (Serra dos Tucanos), 2010 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Panama (Canopy Tower + Ext.), 2011 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Ted Chandik Bird Notes, 1957-58 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Ted Chandik Bird Notes, 1961-62 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Ted Chandik Bird Notes, 1951-52 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Ted Chandik, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Ted Chandik List of Birds + Mammals seen in East Africa, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Ted Chandik Bird Notes, 1959-60 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Ted Chandik Bird Notes, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Ted Chandik Bird Notes, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Ted Chandik Bird Notes, 1955-56 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Birder's Life, List and Diary, 1960-75 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Birds of California, undated (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Slides, 1958-2006
  - Baja California, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Desert Trips - Sierras/Mono Lake, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - State Scenery - Hawaii/Florida, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Alaska, Texas, Japan, Cuba, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Spain, Brazil, Nepal, Madagascar, Palm Springs, CA, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Australia/Bolivia, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - New Zealand, Galapagos, Ecuador, Mexico, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - New Zealand, David Starr Jordan, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - West Indies, Trinidad and Tobago, Galapagos Islands, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Oaxaca - Chiabas, 1991 Nov (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Mexico, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Mexico, Costa Rica, Guatemala, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Peru, Argentina, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - East Africa, Colombia, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Aradiam, Oman, Spain, South Africa, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - India, Yosemite, Baja CA, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Philippines, Papua New Guinea, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Uganda, South Africa, Suriname, Chile, Sierra Leone, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Bird Nests, Teaching Slides, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - California Plants, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - California Plants, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Land Birds, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Water Birds, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Animals, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Mosses, Fungi, Liverworts, Insects, Yard Flowers - Indiana, Rose Handslides - Flowers, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Plants of Baja, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Trin. / Tob. Costa Rica, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Tropical Families, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Birds and Jasper Ridge and Yard, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Flora del Ecuador #1, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Color Slides, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Venezuela, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Miami -> Nassau Cruise #1, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Nassau -> Fish St. Thomas, St. Martin #2, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - New Quinea, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Identified Peruvian Plants A-ERI #1, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Peruvian Plants EUP-O, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Costa Rica Flowers & Fruit, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Tropical Flowers Slides A-P, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Costa Rica - Plants by Family, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Peru Slides P-Z, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - General Peru Slides #1, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Plants of Baja, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Costa Rica General, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Flora del Ecuador #2, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - St. Thomas Cruise -> St. Maarten #3, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Tropical Flowers Slides P-Z, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Elko-Bountiful SLC - Las Vegas - Ind., 1960 Aug - 1961 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Dugway, Utah and Area, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous by Zoe, 1958-1961 (Box 10, Folder 22)